Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
- Recordings
  - [Jacob] Druckman; [William] Schuman; [Michael] Hennegin, gss_933; Two tapes in the same box (gss_933 and gss_934).; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Jacob Druckman: Four Madrigals; William Schuman: Prelude; Michael Hennagin: The House on the Hill: A Madrigal Cantata
  - Early American (1), 11/08/1974; gss_793; Could be "A Gift to be Simple – Music for Early America".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Early American (2), 11/08/1974; gss_794; Could be "A Gift to be Simple – Music for Early America".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Early American (3), 11/08/1974; gss_795; Could be "A Gift to be Simple – Music for Early America".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Edited second side and Outtakes, gss_910; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Ein feste Burg Concert; Peace Lutheran Choir anthem; William Billings: "I heard a great voice", 02/20/1972; gss_921; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Oversize 61)
  - A Festival of Folksongs, Vol. I. (Continental Europe and British Isles) (test copy), 06/17/1982; gss_853; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Ross Lee] Finney (1), gss_916; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - [Ross Lee] Finney (2), gss_888; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Flucas; [Walter] Piston, gss_541; Recording of Lukas Foss's "Behold, behold"; "I build a house" for pipe organ and chorus; Walter Piston - "Psalm and prayer of David" for chamber orchestra and chorus; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    "Behold, behold"; "I build a house" by Lukas Foss; "Psalm and prayer of David" by Walter Piston for chamber orchestra and chorus
  - [Lukas] Foss (8), gss_030; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - [Lukas] Foss (9), gss_031; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - [Lukas] Foss (10), gss_032; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - [Lukas] Foss: "The Prairie", gss_928; Two reels in the same box (gss_928 and gss_929).; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 21:24 (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Lukas Foss: "The Prairie"
  - [Lukas] Foss: "The Prairie", gss_929; Two reels in the same box (gss_928 and gss_929).; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:35 (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Lukas Foss; "The Prairie"
  - [Lukas] Foss: "Three Airs on O'Hara's Angels" (1), gss_905; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Four songs of the World, 04/07/1982; gss_108; Soundstream production information inserted in the box. Note on the box reads: "GSS from Soundstream tape 1 of 2"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 21:16 (Oversize 48)
    Side A: Au Claire de la Lune; Avec me sabots; Cladjens Blomster; Hymn of the day; Das Lieben bringt gross freud; Edelweis; La Cicirinella; Sakura; Ohara Buschi
  - Four songs of the World, 04/07/1982; gss_109; Soundstream production information inserted in the box. Note on the box reads: "GSS from Soundstream tape 2 of 2"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 19:36 (Oversize 48)
    Side B: Irish Washerwoman; Waly Waly; Scarborough Fair; Oh Jeanie; All through the night
  - Four songs of the World, Volume 1 (digital), 04/07/1982; gss_620; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 40:52 (Oversize 49)
    Side A: Au Claire de la Lune; Avec me sabots; Cladjens Blomster; Hymn of the day; Das Lieben bringt gross freud; Edelweis; La Cicirinella; Sakura; Ohara Buschi; Side B: Irish Washerwoman; Waly Waly; Scarborough Fair; Oh Jeanie; All through the night
  - Ft. Worth: "American", gss_847; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - G. [Gregg] Smith Bible Songs, gss_177; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Children choir with piano accompaniment. Titles when indicated are not definitive - 9 cuts: "It was good", "The Lord is My Shepherd", "I bring you Great Joy".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
  - G. [Gregg] Smith Edited Miscellaneous, gss_178; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Baritone, soprano solos with piano accompaniment."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
  - G. [Gregg] Smith: Aesop, gss_424; Gregg Smith's piece "Aesop's Fables" for tenor, piano, soprano, chorus.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    "No once upon a time"; "There was an old man"
  - G. [Gregg] Smith: As the Hart Pants, gss_257; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Gregg Smith Singers - Founding Years, Side 4 - Secular Revolutionary: Band 1 - Bunker Hill (law); Band 2 - Tributes to Washington; A toast (Hopkinson) [illegible]; Ode to the New York; Funeral Dirge; Band 3 - "Seasons", Belknap; Band 4 - Two versions of consonance [?]; Down steers the bass (Reno); London consonance (Billings); Band 5 - 4 solo songs: Wondrous free (Hopkinson); A Cook; Mischievous bee; Took a wife; Band 6 - Friendship Ode (Lyon)
  - G. Smith: "A time for every purpose", Florida Concert, gss_764; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - [George] Gershwin featuring O Reez, 04/29/1976; gss_876; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [George] Gershwin: "Blue Monday, 11/20/1975; gss_877; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Gloria, [Fred] Thayer, gss_012; Additional information about the location of the concert performers on stage is inserted in the box.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
    I. Glory in excelsis (SSAATTBB); II. Laudamus te (SATB, Solo Quartet, Piano); III. Domine Deus (Soprano solo, Piano); IV. Qui tollis peccata mundi (SATB); V. Quoniam tu solus sanctus (SATB, Solo Quartet, Piano; VI. Cum Sancto Spiritu (SSAATTBB, Solo, Quartet, Piano)
  - GNDLA (22), gss_115; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (23), gss_745; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GNDLA (25), gss_117; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (26), gss_118; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (27), gss_119; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (28), gss_120; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (29), gss_121; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (30), gss_122; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GNDLA (31), gss_224; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Slates: 3101-3104: "The Owl and the Pussycat" (Roz with piano accomp.)3104: ? (flute, Roz solo, French?)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    How beautiful (cont), Take 2. God Was in Jesus (Herbst) (4:30); Take 1 (FS); Take 2 (FS - then on); Take 3 (Slated 2) stops at 30 (continue); Take 3 (continuation); Shout Ye Heavens (Antes) (6:15); 2 - (FS); 3 and 4 only Intro; 5; 6 - stats where choir comes in
  - GNDLA (32), gss_225; Per audio engineer RJH notes written on the box are not corresponding to what is on the recording. Additional notes by RJH read: "Slates: 3201-3207: French (Roz, flute solo)">; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    I - Chorales (Antes) (6:00): 1 - Soul, at this most solemn (T1, T2) (1:15); 2 - Oloro in me fulfill (T1, T2) (0:55); 3 - Resting in the silent grave (T1, T2) (1:15); 4 - What splendid rays (T1, T2) (1:00); 5 - O deepest grief (T1, T2), Insert 1) (1:35); II - Look Ye how my servants (Simon Peter) (2:40), Take 1 and 2; III - How Beautiful (Antes) (4:20), Take 1, Take 2 - incomplete(ran out of tape, complete on Reel 3)
  - GNDLA (33), gss_226; Per audio engineer RJH notes written on the box are not corresponding to what is on the recording. Additional notes by RJH read: "Slates: 3301-3310: (clarinet, vocal trio), same piece of music, multiple takes."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    I - It is our God (Johann Bechler) (3:40): Take 1, Take 2 (used end, channel dropped out in T 1); Insert 1 - Take 1; Insert 2 - Take 1; II - I will freely sacrifice (1:43), Take 5; III - I will mention why living kindness (3:45)
  - GNDLA (34), gss_227; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    Slates: (Art Song): 3401: "Break Heart" (Clarinet, vocal duet); 3402-3406: "My love and I must part..." (Clarinet, vocal duet)
  - GNDLA (35), gss_228; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    Cont'd. from gss_227: Slates: (Art Song): 3501-3512: "Break Heart" (Clarinet, 2 sopranos duet)
  - GNDLA (36), gss_229; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    Cont'd. from gss_228: Slates: (Art Song): 3601-3609; " O Happy..." "Break Heart" (Clarinet, 2 sopranos duet); 3610-3613: "Room..." (Clarinet, tenor - baritone duet)
  - GNDLA (37), gss_230; Per audio engineer RJH the notes on the box don't correspond to the content of the recording; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    Cont'd. from gss_229: Slates: 3701-3716: "Room..." (Clarinet, 1 tenor - 1 baritone duet); 3716-3717: "My Love..." (Sopranos, tenors, baritones, clarinet)
  - GNDLA (38), gss_231; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    Cont'd. from gss_230: Slates: 3801-3812: "My Love..."; 3813: "Lyda and the Swan" (Sopranos, piano, tenors, baritones)
  - GNDLA (39), gss_232; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: "Second Session" (Cont'd from 231); 3901-3909: "Lida ... Swan"
  - GNDLA (40), gss_233; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates (Cont'd from 232): 4001-4008: "Lida ... Swan"
  - GNDLA (41), gss_234; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates (Cont'd from 233): 4101-4109: "Lida ... Swan"
  - GNDLA (42), gss_235; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates "Section 8" (Cont'd from 234): 4202-4210: "Lida ... Swan"
  - GNDLA (43), gss_236; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates "Section 8" (Cont'd from 235): 4202-4204: "Lida ... Swan"
  - GNDLA (44), gss_237; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 4401: "The Silver Clock...", "But Where Shall I bury..." (piano, baritone, bass); 4402: ?; 4403-4407: "... Lovely Things Embark..." (piano, baritone, bass); 4408: "The Silver Clock" (piano, baritone, bass); 4409: "Clay..." (piano, baritone, bass); 4410: ? (piano, baritone, bass); 4411: "Dead" (piano, baritone, bass)
  - GNDLA (45), gss_086; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Ros and baritone with piano accompaniment, 1:03 gap at end then fragment - Ros".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GNDLA (46), gss_087; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Soprano solos and duets with piano".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GNDLA (47), gss_088; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Soprano duets with piano. "Suddenly a strange figure appeared...", cast wtih piano and percussion accompaniment. "Reggie..." piano, percussion, cast".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GNDLA (48), gss_089; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Good evening...", cast. "Major 3rd", "Adriatic Sea", "Mobez Air" [?]; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GNDLA (49) (has 48 slates), gss_090; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: About the French environment GNDLA. (opera? Piano, percussion)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - GNDLA (50), gss_091; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "About the French environment GNDLA. (opera? Piano, percussion)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - GNDLA (51), gss_092; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "About the French environment GNDLA. (opera? Piano, percussion)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - GNDLA (52), gss_093; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "About the French environment GNDLA. (opera? Piano, percussion)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - GNDLA (53), gss_094; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "About the French environment GNDLA. (empty cans...)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - GNDLA (Z17), gss_740; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GNDLA (Z18), gss_741; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GNDLA (Z19), gss_742; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GNDLA (Z20), gss_743; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - [Charles] Gounod (11), gss_595; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Greenville Concert: "Lullaby"; popular songs, gss_752; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Gregg Smith - [Francis] Hopkinson etc., gss_924; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Reel IV: "Revolutionary Secular": Band 1 - Banker Hill; Band 2 - Four Tributes to Washington; Band 3 - The Seasons; Band 4 - 2 versions of one text: a - Down steers the bass; b - Consonance; Band 5 - 4 solos ballads; Band 6 - Friendship Odes
  - Gregg Smith - [Francis] Hopkinson etc., gss_925; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Reel VI: "Hopkinson Songs": Band 1 - "Come fair Rosina"; 2 - "My love is gone to sea"; 3 - Beneath a weeping willow"; 4 - "Over the Hills"; 5 - "See down Maria's cheek"; 6 - "Enraptured I gaze"; 7 - "My Generous Heart Disdains"; 8 - "The Traveler"
  - Gregg Smith (10), 11/03/1975; gss_610; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Gregg Smith (11), 11/03/1975; gss_611; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Gregg Smith (12), 11/03/1975; gss_612; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Gregg Smith (1), 04/08/1976; gss_365; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    1-2: "Hallelujah" (mixed choir, unaccomp., No slates); 3: 101-102: "Hallelujah" (mixed choir, unaccomp., No slates)
  - Gregg Smith (2), 04/08/1976; gss_366; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    201-202: "Hallelujah" (mixed choir, unaccomp.); 203-204: "Anyone lived in a ..." (oboe, clarinet, or flute, accomp.)
  - Gregg Smith (3), 04/08/1976; gss_367; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    301: ? (oboe, clarinet or flute, accomp., mixed choir); 302: Measure 33 (oboe, clarinet or flute, accomp., mixed choir); 303-308: 65 thru 73 (oboe, clarinet or flute, accomp., mixed choir); 309: measure 10 (oboe, clarinet or flute, accomp., mixed choir)
  - Gregg Smith (4), 04/08/1976; gss_368; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    401: Cont'd from 367 (mixed choir with instrumentation); 402-406: "Lets tuch the sky..." (mixed choir with instrumentation); 407: "measure 28 insert" (mixed choir with instrumentation)
  - Gregg Smith (5), 04/08/1976; gss_369; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    501: "On the beach at night" (orchestra, mixed chorus)
  - Gregg Smith (6), 04/08/1976; gss_370; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    601: (orchestra, mixed chorus); 602: "Letter K start" "Tempo by J"; 603-605: "be patient" (orchestra, mixed chorus)
  - Gregg Smith (7), 04/08/1976; gss_371; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    701: "... dear child..." (orchestra, mixed chorus); 702: "letter U" (orchestra); 703: "letter U" (orchestra, mixed chorus); 704: "Gloria in Excelsis Deo" (orchestra, mixed chorus)
  - Gregg Smith (8), 04/08/1976; gss_372; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    801/804: "Gloria" cont'd (orchestra, mixed chorus); 805: (string orchestra, 2 altos solo, Latin language, mixed chorus)
  - Gregg Smith (9), 04/08/1976; gss_373; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    901: "95: Gloria" cont'd (orchestra, mixed chorus, altos solo, tenors solo); 902: "Amen" (orchestra, mixed chorus, altos solo, tenors solo); 903: "Kyriae" (orchestra, men's chorus)
  - Gregg Smith (10), 04/08/1976; gss_374; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1001: "Kyriae" (no music); 904: (orchestra, boy's chorus); 1005: ?
  - Gregg Smith (11), 04/08/1976; gss_375; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1101: "Sanctus" "Hosanna in Excelsis" (orchestra, mixed chorus, the telephone); 1102: ?
  - Gregg Smith (12), 04/09/1976; gss_376; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1201-1202: "The harmony of morning" (chorus, orchestra)
  - Gregg Smith (13), 04/09/1976; gss_377; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1301-1308: "The harmony of morning" (chorus, orchestra)
  - Gregg Smith (14), 04/09/1976; gss_378; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1401-1405: "The harmony of morning" (chorus, orchestra); 406: ? (chorus, orchestra)
  - Gregg Smith (15), 04/09/1976; gss_379; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1501-1507: "Orders, orders, orders by the thousands" "Shirt" (tenor solo, chorus, orchestra)
  - Gregg Smith (16), 04/09/1976; gss_380; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    1601: "My good friends don't praise me..." (tenor alto chorus, orchestra); 1602-1603: "Mine", George Gershwin and Ira from "Let them eat cake" and "Sins of Spring"; 1607: "In the Mandarin's orchid garden" from "East is West" (piano, soprano solo - Roz); 1608: "Insent tempo 1" says Roz
  - Gregg Smith (17), 04/09/1976; gss_381; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 27)
    Cont'd from 380: 1701/1703: "In the Mandarins Orchard Garden" (soprano solo Roz with piano); 1704: insert for above
  - Gregg Smith Renwick (1), gss_591; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Gregg Smith Renwick (2), gss_592; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Gregg Smith Renwick (3), gss_593; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Gregg Smith Renwick (4), gss_594; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Gregg Smith Singers - Harold Blumenfeld: Songs of War, 01/16/1973; gss_462; Recording of Harold Blumenfeld's: "Songs of War".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
  - Gregg Smith Xmas [Christmas], gss_550; 1 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - Gregg Smith Xmas [Christmas], gss_561; 1 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - Gregg Smith: [George] Gershwin, Saranac, Roz, Whitman, gss_258; Note reads: Transferred to "Historical 20th Century"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    "O Little Buttercup" by Strauss (from MGM Picture), (soprano, piano); "An American In Paris" (1936 Gershwin) (Geo and Ira); "Good Morning, how Do You Do" (chorus and orchestra, tenor, soprano duet); "Mine" by Gershwin, from "Let Em Eat Cake" (Geo and Ira)
  - Gregg Smith: [Irving] Fine and [Louise] Talma, gss_942; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - Gregg Smith: "Mighty Casey", gss_941; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Mighty Casey [A Baseball Opera]" by William Schuman; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 32:30 (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - Gregg Smith: Jazz Mazz and Benediction, gss_777; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Gregg Smith: Moravian [sic], gss_943; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Gregg Smith: The Continental Harmonist, gss_557; 1/2 inch audio tape; running time 27:00 (Oversize 45)
  - Grenadilla (1), 1979; gss_892; Based on the GSS discography on their website, these are most likely Anthony Philip Heinrich: The Minstrel's Catch; Thomson, Virgil (1896-1989): Half an Alphabet; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    [Anthony Philip ] Heinrich: "Catch"; [Virgil] Thomson: "Alphabet Canon" (last takes on No. 2)
  - Grenadilla (2), 1979; gss_893; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely Thomson, Virgil (1896-1989): Half an Alphabet.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Virgil] Thomson: "Alphabet Canon" (last takes)
  - Grenadilla (7), 1977; gss_912; Note on the box reads: "Portion of chauson missing from this tape (present on 30 ips)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
    [Wolfgang Amadeus] Mozart - Eser; Saunders; Breath Band; Every time (beg.)
  - Grenadilla Miscellaneous (12), 1977; gss_911; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Owl and the Pussy-Cat" by Igor Stravinsky; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
    [Gabriel] Faure; "Owe and Pussy cat"
  - Grenadilla Miscellaneous (9), 1977; gss_913; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The 3-Way Canon Blues" by Henry Brant. Note on the box reads: "this tape may be unsteady through 2103".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
    Orchard; [Arnold] Schoenberg: Lullaby; 3 Way Blues
  - GRNDLA (21), gss_744; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GRNDLA (24), gss_116; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - GRNDLA (X1), gss_724; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (X2), gss_725; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (X3), gss_726; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (X4), gss_727; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (X5), gss_728; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (X6), gss_729; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Y10), gss_733; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Y11), gss_734; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Y12), gss_735; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Y13), gss_736; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Y8), gss_731; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Y9), gss_732; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (YX7), gss_730; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - GRNDLA (Z14), gss_737; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GRNDLA (Z15), gss_738; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GRNDLA (Z16), gss_739; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GS - Grenadilla (1012 A), gss_930; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Music of Edmund Najera. Secundum Lucam (According to Luke)". [LP: Grenadilla Records GS 1012; released 1977]; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - GS - Grenadilla (1012 B), gss_931; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "The Music of Edmund Najera. Secundum Lucam (According to Luke)". [LP: Grenadilla Records GS 1012; released 1977]; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - GS for Susam/Rorem, gss_174; Notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "1 - sopranos, tenors, basses, unaccomp.; 2 - sopranos, tenors, basses, unaccomp."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
  - GS Grenadilla (1034A), gss_613; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - GS Grenadilla (1034B), gss_614; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - GS Magnificat SL, 1981; gss_763; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GS Prayer for Peace, gss_175; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
    1: "Prayer for Peace" (orchestra, women's chorus, mixed chorus, children's chorus)
  - GSS (1), 01/25/1982; gss_641; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (1): [Charles] Ives; [Benjamin] Britten: "St. Cecilia", 01/25/1982; gss_658; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - GSS (2), 01/25/1982; gss_642; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (3), 01/25/1982; gss_643; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (4), 01/25/1982; gss_644; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (5), 01/25/1982; gss_645; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (6), 01/25/1982; gss_646; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (7), 01/25/1982; gss_647; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (8), 01/25/1982; gss_648; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - GSS (1), 05/10/1982; gss_624; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (2), 05/10/1982; gss_625; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (3), 05/10/1982; gss_626; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (3) - [Ann] Silsbee Donna Nobis Pacem, 05/10/1982; gss_768; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - GSS (4), 05/10/1982; gss_627; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (5), 05/10/1982; gss_628; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (6), 05/10/1982; gss_629; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (7), 05/10/1982; gss_630; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (8), 05/10/1982; gss_631; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - GSS (1), Jan 1983; gss_296; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Slates: 101-106: "sing to the Lord" (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), Jan 1983; gss_297; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Slates: 201-203: "Sing to the Lord" (piano, mixed chorus); 204-206: "See that you..." (unaccomp.)
  - GSS (3), Jan 1983; gss_298; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Content cont's from 297" Slates: 301: "Hush..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 302: "But to be corruptible ..." (mixed chorus, tenor solo, unaccomp.); 303-305: "See that you" (mixed chorus, tenor solo, unaccomp.); 306: "Sing songs unto our king" (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (4), Jan 1983; gss_299; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Content cont's from 298" Slates: 401-404: "Sing songs unto our king" (piano, mixed chorus); 405-409: "Surely myself I have come home" (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (5), Jan 1983; gss_300; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Content cont's from 299" Slates: 501-503: "Sure myself I have come home..." ( mixed chorus); 504-506: (acapella version of 502-503); 507-508: 23rd psalm (tenors, piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (6), Jan 1983; gss_301; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Content cont's from 300. Slates: 601-609: "23rd psalm" (tenor, mixed chorus, piano)
  - GSS (7), Jan 1983; gss_302; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Content cont's from 301. Slates: 701-708: "23rd psalm" (acapella)
  - GSS (1), 03/14/1983; gss_303; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)